Lead us into temptation.
Original Sin is a thriller, drama, mystery film directed by Michael Cristofer.
A young man is plunged into a life of subterfuge, deceit and mistaken identity in
pursuit of a femme fatale whose heart is never quite within his grasp.
Julia Russell / Bonnie Castle, played by Angelina Jolie.
Luis Antonio Vargas, played by Antonio Banderas.
Walter Downs / Billy / Mephisto, played by Thomas Jane.
Colonel Worth, played by Gregory Itzin.
Alan Jordan, played by Jack Thompson.
Augusta Jordan, played by Allison Mackie.
Original Sin is a 2001 American erotic romantic thriller film written and directed by
Michael Cristofer and starring Antonio Banderas and Angelina Jolie.
It is based on the 1947 novel Waltz into Darkness by Cornell Woolrich, which was
previously made into the 1969 François Truffaut film Mississippi Mermaid.
The film was produced by actress Michelle Pfeiffer's
production company, Via Rosa Productions.
The film explores themes of cuba, female lover, eroticism, coffee grower, sin.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.